https://weeklyworldnews.com/privacy-policy-2/

GENERAL
WeeklyWorldNews.com is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors and has prepared the following statement to inform users how personally identifying information and non-personally identifying information is gathered from this site and used. This policy may be updated from time to time, so please check back periodically. Please note that this site is intended for use by residents of the United States, its territories and possessions (“U.S.”) only and, therefore, this Privacy Policy is specifically directed only towards residents of the U.S. WeeklyWorldNews.com makes no representation or warranty that content on the site is appropriate or available for use in locations outside of the U.S., and accessing it from territories where the content is illegal is prohibited. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the U.S. and you participate in activities on this site contrary to our policy that only U.S. residents are eligible to use the site, you do so at your own risk and initiative, and are responsible for compliance with any applicable local and national laws. Please be aware that any personally identifying information you transfer to us will be transferred to and processed in the U.S and subject to U.S. law. By using this site, participating in any site activities, and/or providing us with your personally identifying information, you consent to this transfer and processing of personally identifying information to the U.S., and waive any claims that may arise under your own local and national laws.
INFORMATION GATHERING AND USE
Certain non-personally identifiable information about our visitors is collected by the standard operation of WeeklyWorldNews.com internet servers and through the use of “cookie” technology. A “cookie” is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. WeeklyWorldNews.com, like other websites, uses cookies to remind us of who you are, estimate our audience size, and measure visiting and traffic patterns, among other things.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here
Advertisers that serve ads onto WeeklyWorldNews.com may also use their own cookies. You have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those WeeklyWorldNews.com features that require registration in order to participate.
WeeklyWorldNews.com reserves the right to disclose or otherwise utilize non-personally identifiable information collected by the standard operation of our internet servers and through the use of cookies for any purpose, in its sole judgment.
WeeklyWorldNews.com also collects personally identifiable information (such as your name, street address, telephone number and e-mail address) from voluntary submissions as part of site registration, online promotions, merchandise purchases, etc.
Personally identifiable information will be used by WeeklyWorldNews.com (A) to process your requests (e.g., fulfill your merchandise order); (B) to communicate with you or make related offers to you; (3) to administer the WeeklyWorldNews.com website; and/or (4) as may be required by any applicable laws, rules or regulations or the Terms and Conditions applicable to this website.
Personally identifiable information will be shared with third parties to further any and all purposes for which you provide such information or when WeeklyWorldNews.com believes in its sole discretion that the law or regulatory obligations requires it, or to protect the rights of WeeklyWorldNews.com or its parent companies. In addition, WeeklyWorldNews.com reserves the right to transfer such information to a third party in the event of corporate restructuring.
INFORMATION GATHERING BY THIRD PARTY-SITES
WeeklyWorldNews.com advertisers or sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those sites linked to WeeklyWorldNews.com are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we have no control over those sites’ use of such information.
SECURITY
No data transmitted over the Internet can be ensured to be 100% secure. While WeeklyWorldNews.com will use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, personal information submitted to WeeklyWorldNews.com is done so at your own risk.
Search for:
Weekly World News's Stories
Weekly World News's StoriesWWN STUFF FOR THE HOLIDAYS! https://www.hellomerch.com/collections/weekly-world-news
SANTA HAS COVID!
DRACULA GOES VEGAN!
